# Echika Raphael

A Work Loving Software Developer with 2 years of experience who is comfortable with React, JavaScript, HTML/CSS and responsive web design to deliver customer experience with proven experience in creating and designing software in a test-driven environment.

**EXPERIENCE** 

**Side Hustle Internship,** Nigeria — Software Development and Public Speaking

MAY 2021 - DEC 2021

Present for more than 95% of the live classes

Worked as a team leader for the Public Speaking course that took place through the period of my Internship.

Contributed to 10% of the team codebase

Designed a website and worked closely with my mentor.

Assisted in creating a website with the use of Tailwind CSS - A CSS framework

Learned React - A JavaScript library for building user interfaces.

**ZURI Internship**, Nigeria — Software Development

MAY 2022 - AUG 2022

Intern

Created my resume.

Learned CSS Layouts - Grid and Flex boxes

Used my knowledge of Javascript to create an interactive page.

Created my first website using advanced knowledge of HTML and CSS.

Created a mimicry of the zuri homepage.

**HNG Internship**, Nigeria — Software Development

SEP 2022 - NOV 2022

Intern

7, Ekoro Road, Lagos, Nigeria.

+234 708 570 6889

echikaraphael@gmail.com

**GITHUB ACCOUNT** 

https://github.com/Echika

LINKEDIN ACCOUNT

https://www.linkedin.com/in/echika-raphael-b07b96216

**HARD SKILLS** 

HTML

CSS

**JavaScript** 

React

Tailwind CSS

**Public Speaking** 

**SOFT SKILLS** 

**Emotional Intelligence** 

Leadership Skills

Strong Work Ethics

Teamwork

Great communication skills

Adaptability

**AWARDS** 

Side hustle Certificate

Jobberman Certificate

**ZURI** Certificate

**HNG Certificate** 

Most hardworking group

leader

Created my resume.

Learned CSS Layouts - Grid and Flex boxes

Used my knowledge of Javascript to create an interactive page.

Created my first website using advanced knowledge of HTML and CSS.

Created a mimicry of the zuri homepage.

### **LANGUAGES**

Fluent English, Yoruba

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Side Hustle Internship,** Nigeria — Software Development and Public Speaking

MAY 2021 - DEC 2021

Intern

Worked as a team leader for the Public Speaking course that took place through the period of my Internship.

Designed a website and worked closely with my mentor.

Assisted in creating a website with the use of Tailwind CSS - A CSS framework

Learned React - A JavaScript library for building user interfaces.

### **EDUCATION**

ANGLICAN GRAMMAR SCHOOL, OGUN STATE, NIGERIA. SSCE.

BEELRAPH COMPUTER INSTITUTE, LAGOS

WEB DEVELOPMENT.

### **PROJECTS**

echika.github.io/agecalculator